inwin-style.com 2018-12-04

# InWin Privacy Policy

In Win Development Inc. respects and promises to protect your privacy. We comply with all of the privacy laws, and all other personal information related regulations in Taiwan. Please review the explanation below and see if it might answer some of your questions and ease your concerns.

Navigating or using the services provided by this website means you consent with our privacy policy, which includes how we collect, store, process or use your personal information.

## How we collect and use your personal information

When you are navigating or using the provided service, you can decide whether you want to become our member, ask for technical support, or register your purchased product or not. However, some services might ask you to provide your personal information like your name, phone number, living address, e-mail, etc. Those pieces of information are used to complete the desired services in a more efficient and effective manner. Most collected information is the same information generally offered voluntarily by participants during events like contests, promotional activities, and raffle drawings.

The collected information is mainly used for “Marketing,” “Consumer, Customer Management and Service,” “Advertisement or commercial behavior administration,” “Internet shopping and other electronic commerce services,” and “Investigation, statistics and research analysis” (The specific purpose code number of Personal Information Protection Act in Taiwan are 040,090,152,148,157). For instances like: personalized technical support, contacting contest winners, responding to questions, conducting experience or satisfaction surveys, providing information, and product promotion.

The personal information we collected in the websites includes the following code types of identification:  
Code 001 Type for identifying individuals  
For example: Name, title, address, phone number, the E-mail address as well as any other data which can identify the individual.  
Code 011 Individual description  
For example: Age, gender, date of birth, etc.

The time period, area, target and way of the use of personal information  
1.Time period: The time period ends by the member request to cease the use.  
2.The Area: The personal informaiton will be used in the sales area of our products.  
3.The target and way of the use of personal information: The personal information of the member will be used for the personal identification, marketing and the research of the comsumer act, ect.

The rights of the member to his personal information  
The member providing his personal information to us could exercise the following rights in accordance with Personal Information Protection Act:  
1\. any inquiry and request for a review of the personal information;  
2\. any request to make duplications of the personal information;  
3\. any request to supplement or correct the personal information;  
4\. any request to discontinue collection, processing or use of personal information; and 5. any request to delete the personal information.  
All members could excersie the forgoing rights via the “[contact us](https://in-win.com/en/contact)” directory on our website

We will not sell your private information to a third party. If there is no need of your private information, we will stop collecting or using your personal information.

## Tracking cookies

Tracking cookies area technique which records and stores the information about how you navigate a specific website in your own computer. The recorded information is used for optimizing user experiences by offering more personalized web pages. We douse tacking cookies in our web pages in order to keep improving our web page design and online ambience for our users.

Tracking cookies are a common practice nowadays with most websites. If you still feel uncomfortable about the use of tracking cookies, most browsers allow you to remove the stored information recorded by tracking cookies. Simply disable the feature to prevent the action. Please note that while you can alter your browser settings to refuse the use of tracking cookies, this might cause malfunctions in some web pages.

## Privacy security

We apply strict privacy protection to avoid your personal information from being stolen, released, destroyed, or altered by others. When we are collecting, storing, transmitting, or using your personal data, strict censorship guidelines are applied and only key personnel are allowed to access or check your personal information.

In addition, we maintain our system regularly to prevent invading hackers or malwares. Therefore, your information is safe no matter if online or offline. That said, we highly recommend you to change your password regularly. We will always try to keep information safe, but you can also help prevent hackers from stealing your information by avoiding the use of simple passwords. The more complicated the password the better, which should consist of a mix of both letters and numbers.

## Check or change your personal information

If you would like to check or change your stored information, you are welcome to log into your account to check or alter your personal details. If you still have any questions about how to alter your stored information, you are welcome to use “[contact us](https://in-win.com/en/contact)”, and we will try to assist you as soon as possible.

## Sensitive information

We will not request you to provide any sensitive information such as: your religion, health records, sexual orientation, political beliefs, criminal records, etc.

## Children privacy principle

In order to protect children’s privacy, we will not consciously collect or use children’s personal information without their parent’s permission. If we discover any inappropriate information in our database, we will delete it immediately. However, we do encourage children to use our services with their parent’s or guardian’s guidance, and only submit their personal information to us when their parents or guardians are aware and have agreed our privacy policy.

## Alteration

We might alter our privacy settings occasionally. We will not notify our members individually, therefore we encourage you to check our privacy policy regularly.

## Contact us

If you still have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, you are welcome to get in touch with our employees via the “[contact us](https://in-win.com/en/contact)” directory on our website.
